PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML/CSS/SASS
- JavaScript and jQuery
- Bootstrap4
- React.js
- APIs and AJAX
- Gulp
- · Git and the command line
- Npm
- Wordpress

PERSONAL SKILLS

- I'm a very sociable person
- Inquisitive
- Dedicated

CONTACT

P: 07477507840 E: s.b.milano@gmail.com W: stefanobisio.github.io

SOCIAL

- github.com/stefanobisio
- in /in/stefanobisio
- @Imallovertheweb

ABOUT

Fully passionate about programming, I come from a background of freelancing and coding autodidact.

My experience in hospitality has given me excellent social and communication abilities.

I have enrolled in a self-funded full-time developers course in 2017 to get myself to market level.

In my portfolio, you can see a few of the project I've been developing for learning and for fun.

I'm focused on building a reputation in the online community and staying on top of today's web programming languages.

EXPERIENCES

• DEVELOPERS PROFESSIONAL PROGRAMME

Just IT Training Ltd, London | June 2017 - Present

The course provides training on the most in-demand skills for developers today, along with career and soft-skills coaching. The topics include HTML and CSS, Javascript and jQuery, C# and ASP.NET

WORKING-STUDYING PERIOD
 London Farringdon | March 2017 - June 2017

I started studying web development while being employed full time in bars. Resources used include Freecodecamp and Codecademy. I started my portfolio, stefanobisio.github.io, and coded a few projects. This is when I decided to fully invest in web development.

HOSPITALITY CAREER
 Farringdon | 2014 - 2017

I learned to work along with small and big teams, learned the training of new members, and most of all to deal with unsatisfied customers of every sort.

OTHER INFO

I'm a driving license holder I'm looking for a position in London I can provide references on request Available immediately

• ORCHID BOX LTD - INTERNSHIP London Bridge | July 2014 - September 2014

I was part of a small team in a shared open-space office in London Bridge. It was very vibrant with start-ups and entrepreneurs. I had my hands on the HTML and CSS, with some SEO work as well.

I took part in the creation of a real-time bidding advertising network called Geniad.

• FREELANCING

Milan, Italy | 2013 - 2014

I've helped small and medium-sized businesses with their online presence by redesigning their websites, setting up their online campaigns and social media marketing.

I learned to deal with clients and gained experience in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator, Wordpress and Joomla.

The latest client online to date is SparkSync.co.uk, providing training and consulting in UK and Uganda.

EDUCATION

ITIS ALBERT EINSTEIN Milan, Italy | 2004 - 2008

Field of study: Electrical, Electronic and Communications Engineering Technology/Technician.

Thank you for your time,

London, 18/11/2017